In this video, I want to
在这个视频中，我想
(字幕整理：中国海洋大学 黄海广,haiguang2000@qq.com )
tell you about how to use neural
告诉你如何使用神经
networks to do multiclass
网络做多类
classification where we may
分类，我们可以
have more than one category
有一个以上的类别
that we're trying to distinguish amongst.
我们正在试图区分之间。
In the last part of
中的最后部分
the last video, where we
最后一个视频，在这里我们
had the handwritten digit recognition
有手写数字识别
problem, that was actually
的问题，这实际上是
a multiclass classification problem because
因为多类分类问题
there were ten possible categories
有十个可能的类别
for recognizing the digits from
从认识数字
0 through 9 and so, if
0至9，所以，如果
you want us to fill you
您希望我们填补你
in on the details of how to do that.
在关于如何做到这一点的细节。
The way we do multiclass classification
我们做的多类分类的方法
in a neural network is essentially
在一个神经网络本质上是
an extension of the one versus all method.
一个与所有方法的延伸。
So, let's say that we
所以，让我们说，我们
have a computer vision example,
有计算机视觉的例子，
where instead of just trying
在那里，而不是只是想
to recognize cars as in
认识到汽车在
the original example that I started off
那我开始了最初的例子
with, but let's say that
用，但让我们说，
we're trying to recognize, you know, four
我们试图认识，你知道，四
categories of objects and given
对象的类别和特定
an image we want to
我们想要的图像
decide if it is a pedestrian, a car, a motorcycle or a truck.
决定是否有行人，汽车，摩托车或卡车。
If that's the case, what
如果是这样的话，有什么
we would do is we would
我们会做的是，我们会
build a neural network with four
建立一个神经网络与四
output units so that
输出单元，使得
our neural network now outputs a vector of four numbers.
我们的神经网络现在输出四个数字的向量。
So, the output now is actually
所以，现在输出实际上是
needing to be a vector of four
无需是四的矢量
numbers and what we're
数字和我们在做什么
going to try to do is
要尝试做的是
get the first output unit
获得第一输出单元
to classify: is the
分类：是
image a pedestrian, yes or no.
图像中的行人，yes或no。
The second unit to classify: is the image a car, yes or no.
第二个单元进行分类：是图像一辆车，是或否。
This unit to classify: is the
本单元进行分类：是
image a motorcycle, yes or
像摩托车，或者是
no, and this would classify:
没有，而这将分类：
is the image a truck, yes or no.
是图像卡车，yes或no。
And thus, when the image
因而，当图像
is of a pedestrian, we
是一行人，我们
would ideally want the network
在理想情况下希望网络
to output 1, 0, 0, 0,
到输出1，0，0，0，
when it is a
当它是一个
car we want it to output
车上我们希望它输出
0, 1, 0, 0, when this
0，1，0，0，当该
is a motorcycle, we get it to or rather, we want
被一辆摩托车，我们得到它或者说，我们要
it to output 0, 0,
它输出到0，0，
1, 0 and so on.
1,0等。
So this is just like
因此，这就像
the "one versus all" method
“一对所有”的方法
that we talked about when we
我们谈到我们时
were describing logistic regression, and
被描述logistic回归，和
here we have essentially four logistic
在这里，我们有四个基本的逻辑
regression classifiers, each of
回归分类器，每个
which is trying to recognize one
这是试图承认一个
of the four classes that
四班的那
we want to distinguish amongst.
我们要区分之间。
So, rearranging the slide of
因此，重新排列幻灯片
it, here's our neural network
它，这里是我们的神经网络
with four output units and those
有四个输出单元和那些
are what we want h
是我们想要的?
of x to be when we
x的是，当我们
have the different images, and
有不同的图像，并
the way we're going to represent the
我们要代表的方式
training set in these settings
培训在这些设置中设置
is as follows. So, when we have
如下。所以，当我们有
a training set with different images
训练集与不同的图像
of pedestrians, cars, motorcycles and
的行人，汽车，摩托车及
trucks, what we're going
卡车，我们要去
to do in this example is
做在这个例子中是
that whereas previously we had
而那之前我们有
written out the labels as
写出来的标签作为
y being an integer from
y是整数
1, 2, 3 or 4. Instead of
1，2，3或4。相反的
representing y this way,
代表?这样一来，
we're going to instead represent y
我们要代替代表?
as follows: namely Yi
如下：即易
will be either 1, 0, 0, 0
将是1，0，0，0
or 0, 1, 0, 0 or 0, 0, 1, 0 or 0, 0, 0, 1 depending on what the
或0，1，0，0或0，0，1，0或0，0，0，1，取决于什么样的
corresponding image Xi is.
相应的图像Xi为。
And so one training example
等一训练实例
will be one pair Xi colon Yi
将一对结肠熙怡
where Xi is an image with, you
其中Xi是一个形象，你
know one of the four objects and
知道有四个对象，并
Yi will be one of these vectors.
易将这些载体之一。
And hopefully, we can find
并希望，我们可以找到
a way to get our
一种方式来获得我们
Neural Networks to output some
神经网络的输出部分
value. So, the h of x
值。因此，x的?
is approximately y and
大约是y和
both h of x and Yi,
x和毅小时，
both of these are going
这两个要
to be in our example,
要在我们的例子中，
four dimensional vectors when we have four classes.
当我们有四个类四维向量。
So, that's how you
所以，这是你如何
get neural network to do multiclass classification.
得到的神经网络做多类分类。
This wraps up our discussion on
这个部分是我们的讨论
how to represent Neural Networks
如何表示神经网络
that is on our hypotheses representation.
这是对我们的假设表示。
In the next set of videos, let's
在下一组的视频，让我们
start to talk about how take
开始谈论如何利用
a training set and how to
训练集，以及如何
automatically learn the parameters of the neural network.
自动学习神经网络的参数。